

52, 11th Main Road

Banashankari Stage II

Bengaluru, INDIA 560070

▼ WHC9+8C BSK

& +91 97398 56528

್ಲಿ varungupta3009

★ varungupta3005
 ★ //VRG.design/

Experience



Penetration Tester

Center for Information Security, Forensics and Cyber Resilience May 2020 – Present (4 mos)



Student Lead in Network Security and Web Development

Developer Student Clubs • PES University Jan 2019 – Present (1 yr 8 mos)



Software Engineer

Mindtree

Jul 2019 - Feb 2020 (8 mos)

Education



PES University

Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science & Engineering 2017 – 2021



R. V. PU College

Pre-University, Affiliated to NCERT, New Delhi, Computer Science 2015 – 2017



Carmel School, Padmanabhanagar

ICSE, New Delhi — SSLC, Karnataka 2002 - 2015

Publications & Awards

Software Implementation of an Automatic Movable Road Barrier IEEE, October 2019, ISBN: 978-1-7281-1576-4

Prof. C N R Rao Merit Scholarship PES University, November 2019

Licenses and Certifications

Associate Cloud Engineer

Google, August 2020

Languages

English Hindi Kannada

Hobbies

□ Reading

🛣 Virtual Aviation



Knowledge and Skills

Python 3 Experience	
Skill	
JavaScript Experience Skill	
C/C++ Experience Skill	
Java, C#, Go Experience Skill	
Experience	sign and Development
Skill Full-Stack Wo Experience Skill	eb Development
	React (JS/TS)
WordPress, (Experience Skill	CMS
Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator Experience	
Skill	
Experience	Effects and Premiere Pro
Skill	ar Renderman
Experience Skill	
Cloud Architechture (GCP) Experience	
Skill	

About me

I am a programmer and experienced web-developer, fluent in Python, C++, C#, Go with over 9 years of experience in Python and C++, and moderately versed in 7 other languages. I am a polymath and love to explore and try new technologies and fiddling with anything related to computers or the Windows OS in general. I am also a graphics designer and a hobbyist hacker.

I recommend checking out my LinkedIn Profile for real-time accurate information, to stay regularly updated and get in touch with me instantly.

